

Hasin Rayan

Address: F-137, 10/7. J Block, South Banasree, Dhaka-1219

Phone: 01931584514

Email: <u>hasinrayan27@gmail.com</u>

OBJECTIVE

Pursuing a position in the mechanical design industry in which I can utilize and build upon my education, skills and past experiences in a way that is mutually beneficial to both and employer and allow for future growth and advancement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAD Operator at *Tokyo Electric Power Service Co.*

Office: Matarbari Joint Venture Consultant

117, Kazi Nazrul Islam Avenue, Unique Height(18th Floor) Project: Matarbari USC Coal fired Power Plant.

11th January, 2022 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Develop technical drawings using CAD software
- Make revisions and obtain approval from the Project Manager
- Prepare supporting documentation that includes product materials and dimensions
- Distribute drawings to internal departments and external contractors

Assistant Engineer at *KDS Logistics Ltd.*

Sonaichari, Kumira, Chitagong-4314

1st January, 2020 - 10 January, 2022

Responsibilities:

- Inspect vehicle engine and mechanical/electrical components to diagnose issues accurately
- Conduct routine maintenance work (replacing fluids, lubricating parts etc.) aiming to vehicle functionality and longevity
- Schedule future maintenance sessions and advise motorists on good vehicle use
- Repair or replace broken or dysfunctional parts and fix issues (e.g. leaks)
- Provide accurate estimates (cost, time, effort) for a repair or maintenance job
- Keep logs on work and issues
- Maintain equipment and tools in good condition

WORK EXPERIENCE

Site Engineer at *Conveyor Logistics Ltd.*

57 Kemal Ataturk Avenue Banani C/A, Dhaka 1213

5 January, 2019 - 29 December, 2019

Responsibilities:

- Logistics Operations
- Site Management
- Client Services
- Customer Related Matters

EDUCATION

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Feni Govt. Pilot High School.
Passed with GPA 4.63 out of 5.00
Commerce Section

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering

Feni Polytechnic Institute Passed with GPA 2.86 out of 4.00 (Passing Year 2017)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Trainings /

Certifications

- Solidworks
- AutoCAD
- Microsoft Word
- Adobe Illustrator
- Mobile Application Development
- MasterCAM
- CNC Machine
- Microsoft Excel
- Adobe Photoshop
- Technical Drawing
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- WordPress Development

Github: https://github.com/zidni02

Cad & Cam Design and ProgrammingBEIOA-Light Engineering Training Institute (SEIP & ADB)

Paradise Bhaban, 2 Folder Street, Wari, Dhaka

Duration: 25th April To 25th October, 2018

Topic Covered:

Solidworks, Master Cam, C.N.C. Machine, Technical Drawing

Auto Cad 2D & 3D

Bangladesh Industrial and Technical Assistance Center (BITAC)

Sagorica Road, Chittagong-4219

Duration: 20th August to 28th September, 2017

Topic Covered:

AutoCAD Software, Technical Drawing

Industrial Attachment

Bangladesh Industrial and Technical Assistance Center (BITAC) Sagorica Road, Chittagong-4219

Duration: 1st August to 26th September, 2017

Trainings / Certifications

Android Application Development

National Academy for Computer Training and Research (NACTAR)

[Govt.]

Duration: 1 Month (January, 2021)

Topic Covered:

Android Studio IDE, Android Programming, JAVA OOP, Android

Layout Design in XML Coding

Personal Information

Name : Hasin Rayan.
Father's Name : Rezaul Karim.
Mother's Name : Khaleda Sultana.

Permanent Address : 456, Mizan Road, Feni Sadar.

Date of Birth : 27th November, 1997. Nationality : Bangladeshi (By Birth).

Religion : Islam. Marital Status : Single.

Mobile : +8801931584514

References

Mohammed Shahid Ullah

Executive Director (Finance)

Company: Coal Power Generation Company Bangladesh

Limited (CPGCBL)

Address: Unique Heights (Level 17), 117, Kazi Nazrul Islam

Avenue, Dhaka-1217.

Cell: +8801730798097, +8801716383259.

Candidate Signature